Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) Records UA032
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Accreditation Files, 1973 -- 2000; 1973 -- 1984; UA032.006; 3.4 Linear Feet
  - BSOT Accreditation Application [Binder 4 of 4], 1977; UA032.006.132.00015 (Box 132)
  - Masters Proposal, 1979; UA032.006.132.00016 (Box 132)
  - BSOT Basic Masters Degree Program Accreditation Application [Binder 1 of 4], 1979; UA032.006.132.00017 (Box 132)
  - BSOT Basic Masters Degree Program Accreditation Application [Binder 2 of 4], 1979; UA032.006.132.00018 (Box 132)
  - BSOT Basic Masters Degree Program Accreditation Application [Binder 3 of 4], 1979; UA032.006.132.00019 (Box 132)
  - BSOT Basic Masters Degree Program Accreditation Application [Binder 4 of 4], 1979; UA032.006.132.00020 (Box 132)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation [Binder 1 of 4], 1983; UA032.006.132.00021 (Box 132)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation [Binder 2 of 4], 1983; UA032.006.133.00001 (Box 133)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation [Binder 3 of 4], 1983; UA032.006.133.00002 (Box 133)
  - Application for Continuing Accreditation [Binder 4 of 4], 1983; UA032.006.133.00003 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation for an Educational Program for the Occupational Therapist [Binder 1 of 3], 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00004 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation for an Educational Program for the Occupational Therapist [Binder 2 of 3], 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00005 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation for an Educational Program for the Occupational Therapist [Binder 3 of 3], 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00006 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation, 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00007 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation Appendix I [Binder 1 of 2], 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00008 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation Appendix I [Binder 2 of 2], 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00009 (Box 133)
  - Application for Accreditation Appendix II, 1983 -- 1984; UA032.006.133.00010 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Materials [Binder 1 of 4], 1990; UA032.006.133.00011 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Materials, 1990; UA032.006.133.00012 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Materials [Binder 3 of 4], 1990; UA032.006.133.00013 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Materials [Binder 4 of 4], 1990; UA032.006.133.00014 (Box 133)
  - AOTA Evaluators' Manual [Binder 1 of 2], 1990 -- 1993; UA032.006.133.00015 (Box 133)
  - AOTA Evaluators' Manual [Binder 2 of 2], 1990 -- 1993; UA032.006.133.00016 (Box 133)
  - AOTA Accreditation Committee and Manual [Binder 1 of 2], 1991 -- 1993; UA032.006.133.00017 (Box 133)
  - AOTA Accreditation Committee and Manual [Binder 2 of 2], 1991 -- 1993; UA032.006.133.00018 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Report [Binder 1 of 4], 1996; UA032.006.133.00019 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Report [Binder 2 of 4], 1996; UA032.006.133.00020 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Report [Binder 3 of 4], 1996; UA032.006.133.00021 (Box 133)
  - Self Study Report [Binder 4 of 4], 1996; UA032.006.133.00022 (Box 133)
  - AOTA Accreditation Council for Occupational Therapy Education Accreditation Manual, 2000; UA032.006.133.00023 (Box 133)
- Morning Musicales, 1928 -- 1990; 1929 -- 1955; UA032.007; 0.75 Linear Feet; 49 Volumes
  Boston School of Occupational Therapy Morning Musicales (recitals) records containing financial information, music programs and advertisement information.
  Arranged by order that the folders were found in the original boxes.
  - Morning Musicales, 1961 -- 1979; UA032.007.014.00001 (Box 14)
    Articles and photographs of the Morning Musicals
  - Morning Musicales, 1929 -- 1975; UA032.007.014.00002 (Box 14)
    Morning Musicals payment and donation records
  - BSOT Directory, 1961; UA032.007.014.00003 (Box 14)
    Directory of students and graduates of the program as of 1961
  - Morning Musicales Boston Post Magazine Article, 1954; UA032.007.014.00004 (Box 14)
    Article explaining the morning musicales in relation to the BSOT
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 1st season, 1928 -- 1929; UA032.007.051.001 (Box Volume 51)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 2nd season, 1929 -- 1930; UA032.007.052.001 (Box Volume 52)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 3rd season, 1930 -- 1931; UA032.007.053.001 (Box Volume 53)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 4th season, 1931 -- 1932; UA032.007.054.001 (Box Volume 54)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 5th season, 1932 -- 1933; UA032.007.055.001 (Box Volume 55)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 6th season, 1933 -- 1934; UA032.007.056.001 (Box Volume 56)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 7th season, 1934 -- 1935; UA032.007.057.001 (Box Volume 57)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 8th season, 1935 -- 1936; UA032.007.058.001 (Box Volume 58)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 9th season, 1936 -- 1937; UA032.007.059.001 (Box Volume 59)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 10th season, 1937 -- 1938; UA032.007.060.001 (Box Volume 60)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 11th season, 1938 -- 1939; UA032.007.061.001 (Box Volume 61)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 12th season, 1939 -- 1940; UA032.007.062.001 (Box Volume 62)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 13th season, 1940 -- 1941; UA032.007.063.001 (Box Volume 63)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 14th season, 1941 -- 1942; UA032.007.064.001 (Box Volume 64)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 15th season, 1942 -- 1943; UA032.007.065.001 (Box Volume 65)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 16th season, 1943 -- 1944; UA032.007.066.001 (Box Volume 66)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 17th season, 1944 -- 1945; UA032.007.067.001 (Box Volume 67)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 18th season, 1945 -- 1946; UA032.007.068.001 (Box Volume 68)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 19th season, 1946 -- 1947; UA032.007.069.001 (Box Volume 69)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 20th season, 1947 -- 1948; UA032.007.070.001 (Box Volume 70)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 21st season, 1948 -- 1949; UA032.007.071.001 (Box Volume 71)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 22nd season, 1949 -- 1950; UA032.007.072.001 (Box Volume 72)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 23rd season, 1950 -- 1951; UA032.007.073.001 (Box Volume 73)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 24th season, 1951 -- 1952; UA032.007.074.001 (Box Volume 74)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 25th season, 1952 -- 1953; UA032.007.075.001 (Box Volume 75)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 26th season, 1953 -- 1954; UA032.007.076.001 (Box Volume 76)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 27th season, 1954 -- 1955; UA032.007.077.001 (Box Volume 77)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 28th season, 1955 -- 1956; UA032.007.078.001 (Box Volume 78)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 29th season, 1956 -- 1957; UA032.007.079.001 (Box Volume 79)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 30th season, 1957 -- 1958; UA032.007.080.001 (Box Volume 80)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 31st season, 1958 -- 1959; UA032.007.081.001 (Box Volume 81)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 32nd season, 1959 -- 1960; UA032.007.082.001 (Box Volume 82)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 33rd season, 1960 -- 1961; UA032.007.083.001 (Box Volume 83)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 34th season, 1961 -- 1962; UA032.007.084.001 (Box Volume 84)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 35th season, 1962 -- 1963; UA032.007.085.001 (Box Volume 85)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 36th season, 1963 -- 1964; UA032.007.086.001 (Box Volume 86)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 37th season, 1964 -- 1965; UA032.007.087.001 (Box Volume 87)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 38th season, 1965 -- 1966; UA032.007.088.001 (Box Volume 88)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 39th season, 1966 -- 1967; UA032.007.089.001 (Box Volume 89)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 40th season, 1967 -- 1968; UA032.007.090.001 (Box Volume 90)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 41st season, 1968 -- 1969; UA032.007.091.001 (Box Volume 91)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 42nd season, 1969 -- 1970; UA032.007.092.001 (Box Volume 92)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 43rd season, 1970 -- 1971; UA032.007.093.001 (Box Volume 93)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 44th season, 1971 -- 1972; UA032.007.094.001 (Box Volume 94)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 45th season, 1972 -- 1973; UA032.007.095.001 (Box Volume 95)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 46th season, 1973 -- 1974; UA032.007.096.001 (Box Volume 96)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 47th season, 1974 -- 1975; UA032.007.097.001 (Box Volume 97)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 48th season, 1975 -- 1976; UA032.007.098.001 (Box Volume 98)
  - Boston Morning Musicales, 49th season, 1976 -- 1977; UA032.007.099.001 (Box Volume 99)
  - Morning Musicales brochures, 1988 -- 1990; UA032.007.111.00004 (Box UA032 Shared 2)
- Subject Files, 1903 -- 1990; 1940 -- 1960; UA032.008; 13.2 Linear Feet
  Foldered correspondence and subject files of the Boston School of Occupational Therapy. Includes agreements with clinical centers, faculty syllabi, and student health insurance information.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Academic standing of students, degrees with distinction, 1958 -- 1959; UA032.008.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Accreditation, 1964; UA032.008.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Accreditation, 1973; UA032.008.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Admissions, recruitment, 1931-59, 1931 -- 1959; UA032.008.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Admissions reports, 1960 -- 1979; UA032.008.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Allied Health Professions, 1967 -- 1970; UA032.008.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Alumni Association, 1964 -- 1965; UA032.008.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - BSOT alumnae surveys, 1949 -- 1952; UA032.008.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Student alumni luncheon, 1967; UA032.008.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - BSOT AA meetings, 1930 -- 1955; UA032.008.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - AA, 1919 -- 1959; UA032.008.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - BSOT Alumni Association, 1936 -- 1964; UA032.008.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - American Association for Rehabilitation Therapy, Inc., 1955; UA032.008.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - AMA brochure for occupational therapy, 1942; UA032.008.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - American Medical Association, 1937 -- 1938; UA032.008.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - American Medical Association, 1959 -- 1963; UA032.008.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - American Medical Association, 1941 -- 1965; UA032.008.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - AMA Essentials, 1965; UA032.008.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - AMA approved medical schools, 1960; UA032.008.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - American Mutual Liability Insurance Co., 1950; UA032.008.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - American Nurses Association, 1959; UA032.008.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - American P. T. Association, 1960; UA032.008.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Annual Fund, 1965 -- 1969; UA032.008.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - AOTA-CBPE, 1970 -- 1971; UA032.008.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - AOTA enrollment data, 1976; UA032.008.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - AOTA rules and procedures, 1949; UA032.008.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - AOTA resgistration, 1932 -- 1970; UA032.008.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - AOTA student committee, 1972; UA032.008.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education workshop, UA032.008.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - AOTA, 1921 -- 1961; UA032.008.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - AOTA conventions, 1940; UA032.008.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - AOTA, 1963 -- 1968; UA032.008.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education steering committee, 1967 -- 1971; UA032.008.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education steering committee, 1967 -- 1971; UA032.008.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education steering committee, 1972; UA032.008.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education steering committee, subcommittee on schools and curriculum, 1946 -- 1948; UA032.008.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - AOTA education steering committee, educational field secretary Miss McNory's correspondence, 1940 -- 1946; UA032.008.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - AOTA curriculum study, 1963; UA032.008.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - AOTA curriculum study, 1963; UA032.008.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - AOTA-CBPE, 1969; UA032.008.043.00017 (Box 43)
  - AOTA accreditation committee, 1972; UA032.008.043.00018 (Box 43)
  - AOTA: Fox Valley Technical Institute Survey, 1972; UA032.008.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - AOTA-CBPE midwinter 1971, UA032.008.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - AOTA survey: N. H. Voc-Tech, Claremont College, 1973; UA032.008.043.00021 (Box 43)
  - AOTA-OT assistants, 1967; UA032.008.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Antioch College, 1955 -- 1957; UA032.008.043.00023 (Box 43)
  - Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation, 1964 -- 1965; UA032.008.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Association of Rehabilitation Centers, Inc., 1962 -- 1964; UA032.008.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Bay State Society for Crippled and Handicapped, 1964 -- 1965; UA032.008.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - Bequests, 1972; UA032.008.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Board of Visitors, 1933 -- 1968; UA032.008.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Board of Visitors (Managers), resolutions, 1955 -- 1962; UA032.008.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Board of Visitors report, 1965 -- 1967; UA032.008.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - Boston Aid to the Blind, Inc., 1969; UA032.008.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Boston Association for Retarded Children, 1963; UA032.008.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - Boston, City of, 1922 -- 1959; UA032.008.044.00007 (Box 44)
  - Boston City Hospital, 1966; UA032.008.044.00008 (Box 44)
  - BOUVE-Boston School of Physical Education, 1946 -- 1953; UA032.008.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - Boston State Hospital, UA032.008.044.00010 (Box 44)
  - Dedication of A. Warren Stearns Research Building, 1963; UA032.008.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - BSOT Building Fund, 1937 -- 1968; UA032.008.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - Building plans, 1941; UA032.008.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - Buildings, 1960 -- 1963; UA032.008.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - Brochures, 1935; UA032.008.044.00015 (Box 44)
  - Brochures, publications, 1934 -- 1963; UA032.008.044.00016 (Box 44)
  - BSOT by-laws, UA032.008.044.00017 (Box 44)
  - Cambridge Sanitorium, student project, 1948; UA032.008.044.00018 (Box 44)
  - Catalogs, 1926 -- 1947; UA032.008.044.00019 (Box 44)
  - Catalogs, 1949 -- 1954; UA032.008.044.00020 (Box 44)
  - Class gifts, 1962-64, 1962 -- 1966; UA032.008.044.00021 (Box 44)
  - Class letter, 1930; UA032.008.044.00022 (Box 44)
  - Clinical affiliations, 1966 -- 1977; UA032.008.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - Clinical training directors, 1954; UA032.008.044.00024 (Box 44)
  - Clinical directors, January 27, 1956; UA032.008.044.00025 (Box 44)
  - Clinical directors, June 1957, UA032.008.044.00026 (Box 44)
  - Clinical training directors, 1949 -- 1952; UA032.008.044.00027 (Box 44)
  - Clinical directors, 1953; UA032.008.044.00028 (Box 44)
  - Clinical training directors, January 7, 1955; UA032.008.044.00029 (Box 44)
  - Clinical directors, June 1958, UA032.008.044.00030 (Box 44)
  - Child Development Center Journal, 1965 -- 1968; UA032.008.044.00031 (Box 44)
  - Children's Mission to Children, 1951; UA032.008.044.00032 (Box 44)
  - Class gifts, 1924 -- 1959; UA032.008.044.00033 (Box 44)
  - College of Special Studies, 1959 -- 1963; UA032.008.044.00034 (Box 44)
  - College of Special Studies faculty, 1960 -- 1961; UA032.008.044.00035 (Box 44)
  - Commencement Address, 1946 -- 1954; UA032.008.044.00036 (Box 44)
  - Community Workshops, Inc., of Boston, 1963 -- 1970; UA032.008.044.00037 (Box 44)
  - Community Workshops of Rhode Island, Inc., 1952 -- 1963; UA032.008.044.00038 (Box 44)
  - Dorothy Comstock, 1953; UA032.008.044.00039 (Box 44)
  - Conference on Economics of Hospital Care, 1959; UA032.008.044.00040 (Box 44)
  - Conference on Economics of Hospital Care, 1960; UA032.008.044.00041 (Box 44)
  - Conference programs, 1949 -- 1961; UA032.008.044.00042 (Box 44)
  - Constitution, 1959 -- 1962; UA032.008.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - Continuing Education, 1955; UA032.008.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - Continuing Education, 1964 -- 1965; UA032.008.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - Convention programs, 1928 -- 1963; UA032.008.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - BSOT Curriculum, 1960 -- 1972; UA032.008.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum, 1961 -- 1970; UA032.008.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum, 1945 -- 1965; UA032.008.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum, 1945; UA032.008.045.00008 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum, examination samples, UA032.008.045.00009 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1964 -- 1967; UA032.008.045.00010 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum evauations from students, 1960; UA032.008.045.00011 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum summaries, 1963; UA032.008.045.00012 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1958 -- 1970; UA032.008.045.00013 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum study reports, #3 and #4, 1962; UA032.008.045.00014 (Box 45)
  - Curriculum study reports, #10-13, 1963; UA032.008.045.00015 (Box 45)
  - Bacteriology syllabus, 1961; UA032.008.045.00016 (Box 45)
  - Psychopathology, course descriptions, UA032.008.045.00017 (Box 45)
  - OTSI-OT, Introduction, 1966; UA032.008.045.00018 (Box 45)
  - OT 35, Growth and Development, 1961 -- 1963; UA032.008.045.00019 (Box 45)
  - OT 510 Organization and Administration, 1964; UA032.008.045.00020 (Box 45)
  - OT 511 Directed Study, 1964 -- 1968; UA032.008.045.00021 (Box 45)
  - OT 512 Community Agencies, 1963; UA032.008.045.00022 (Box 45)
  - OT 513 Seminar, 1969; UA032.008.045.00023 (Box 45)
  - OTS 17 Physical Dysfunction, 1968; UA032.008.045.00024 (Box 45)
  - OT 530 Orientation to OT 1964, UA032.008.045.00025 (Box 45)
  - OT 5800 Psychiatric summer workshop, 1964; UA032.008.045.00026 (Box 45)
  - OT 53 Physical Disabilities Clerkship, 1964; UA032.008.045.00027 (Box 45)
  - OT 54 and 540 Advanced Physical Disabilities, 1966; UA032.008.045.00028 (Box 45)
  - OT S2 Elementary Physical Disabilities OT S20 Intro to Physical Disabilities, 1963; UA032.008.045.00029 (Box 45)
  - TTS2 Woodworking, 1962; UA032.008.045.00030 (Box 45)
  - TT 51 Design, 1964; UA032.008.045.00031 (Box 45)
  - TT 52 Woodworking, 1948 -- 1964; UA032.008.045.00032 (Box 45)
  - TT 53 Weaving, 1952 -- 1964; UA032.008.045.00033 (Box 45)
  - TT 54 Needlecraft, 1967; UA032.008.045.00034 (Box 45)
  - OTS 5 and 6 Group Dynamics, 1967; UA032.008.045.00035 (Box 45)
  - TT 518 Fundamental Techniques, 1969; UA032.008.045.00036 (Box 45)
  - TT 56 Ceramics, 1957; UA032.008.045.00037 (Box 45)
  - TT 57 and TT 570 Metals and Plastics, 1957 -- 1964; UA032.008.045.00038 (Box 45)
  - TT 58 Advanced Design and Printing and TT 580 Advanced Graphic Art and Printing, 1964; UA032.008.045.00039 (Box 45)
  - TT 59 Group Techniques, 1969; UA032.008.045.00040 (Box 45)
  - TT 511 Pottery, 1964; UA032.008.045.00041 (Box 45)
  - TT 540 Wood, Metals and Plastics, 1964; UA032.008.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - TT 541 Weaving, 1964; UA032.008.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - TT 542 Design and Printing, 1964; UA032.008.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - TT 543 Sewing, 1964; UA032.008.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - OTS 44 Physical Disabilities-exams, 1965; UA032.008.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - Dance therapy, 1967; UA032.008.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Veronica Cavanaugh Dobranske, 1950 -- 1969; UA032.008.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - Dormitory, 1947 -- 1963; UA032.008.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - Easter Seal Society for Crippled Children and Adults, 1969; UA032.008.046.00009 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Marion Easton, 1952; UA032.008.046.00010 (Box 46)
  - Eliot-Pearson School, 1951 -- 1961; UA032.008.046.00011 (Box 46)
  - Equipment inventory, 1942; UA032.008.046.00012 (Box 46)
  - Equipment purchases, 1951 -- 1963; UA032.008.046.00013 (Box 46)
  - Executive Committees, 1925 -- 1938; UA032.008.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - Exhibit for Conferences, 1955 -- 1975; UA032.008.046.00015 (Box 46)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1960 -- 1962; UA032.008.046.00016 (Box 46)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1960 -- 1962; UA032.008.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1962 -- 1965; UA032.008.046.00018 (Box 46)
  - Faculty meeting minutes, 1962 -- 1983; UA032.008.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - Faculty correspondence, 1959 -- 1977; UA032.008.046.00020 (Box 46)
  - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1968; UA032.008.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Audit, FY ending August 31, 1935; UA032.008.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - BSOT report on Audit for 2 years, ending August 31, 1937; UA032.008.046.00023 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Report on Audit, ending August 31, 1938; UA032.008.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Report on Audit, year ending August 31, 1939; UA032.008.046.00025 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1940; UA032.008.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1941; UA032.008.046.00027 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1942; UA032.008.046.00028 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1943; UA032.008.046.00029 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1944; UA032.008.046.00030 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1945; UA032.008.046.00031 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1946; UA032.008.046.00032 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1947; UA032.008.046.00033 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1948; UA032.008.046.00034 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1949; UA032.008.046.00035 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1950; UA032.008.046.00036 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1951; UA032.008.046.00037 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1952; UA032.008.046.00038 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1953; UA032.008.046.00039 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1954; UA032.008.046.00040 (Box 46)
  - BSOT Financial statement, year ending August 31, 1955; UA032.008.046.00041 (Box 46)
  - Marjorie Fish, 1947 -- 1952; UA032.008.046.00042 (Box 46)
  - First Army Emergency Group, 1944; UA032.008.046.00043 (Box 46)
  - Foreign exchange students, 1937 -- 1956; UA032.008.046.00044 (Box 46)
  - Foreign Rehabilitation Centers, 1959; UA032.008.046.00045 (Box 46)
  - Forsyth School for Dental Hygienists, 1955 -- 1959; UA032.008.046.00046 (Box 46)
  - Fundraising, 1922; UA032.008.046.00047 (Box 46)
  - Girl Scouts, 1960; UA032.008.046.00048 (Box 46)
  - Goodwill Industries and Morgan Memorial, 1962; UA032.008.046.00049 (Box 46)
  - Biography of Margorie B. Greene by Veronica C. Dobranske, 1961; UA032.008.046.00050 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Margorie Bell Greene, UA032.008.046.00051 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Margorie Bell Greene, 1952-1958, UA032.008.046.00052 (Box 46)
  - Portrait dedication of Margorie Bell Greene, 1964; UA032.008.046.00053 (Box 46)
  - Correspondence of Margorie Bell Greene, 1971 -- 1975; UA032.008.046.00054 (Box 46)
  - Grenfell Mission, Inc., 1956; UA032.008.046.00055 (Box 46)
  - President Hallowell, inauguration, 1967; UA032.008.046.00056 (Box 46)
  - Hartford Association for Retarded Children, Inc., 1957; UA032.008.046.00057 (Box 46)
  - Hartsborn and Watter, 1940 -- 1959; UA032.008.046.00058 (Box 46)
  - Oscar W. Hausserman, 1924 -- 1951; UA032.008.046.00059 (Box 46)
  - Hebrew Home for the Aged, 1962; UA032.008.047.00001 (Box 47)
    Missing file.
  - BSOT History, 1918 -- 1956; UA032.008.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - BSOT History, 1926 -- 1949; UA032.008.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - History of Profession, 1957 -- 1964; UA032.008.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - House of the Good Shepard, 1955; UA032.008.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Albert B. Hunt, 1959; UA032.008.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - International Society for Welfare of Cripples, International Society for Rehabilitation of Diabetes, 1957; UA032.008.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Institute for the Crippled and Disabled, 1969; UA032.008.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - J.O.B. Boston, 1962; UA032.008.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - John Hancock Life Insurance Co., UA032.008.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Judge Baker Guidance Center, 1962; UA032.008.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1955; UA032.008.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence of Richard Augustus Kelly, 1962 -- 1976; UA032.008.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Kenesiology Manual, UA032.008.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence of Bernice Kinsman, 1949 -- 1961; UA032.008.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Articles and papers of Christine Kris, 1968 -- 1971; UA032.008.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Lab manual, 1959; UA032.008.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Legislative Clearing House, 1965; UA032.008.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Leonard Carmichael Society, 1962 -- 1963; UA032.008.047.00019 (Box 47)